Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
♪ If I could put my problems
in the papers ♪
♪ Then I'd roll them up
and blow them away ♪
♪ If I could find a pill
to solve them ♪
♪ I would take a bottle
and I'd be okay ♪
♪ If life was that easy ♪
♪ Then I'd never have to worry
for the rest of my days ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Thank you, sir.
♪ But life
just ain't that easy ♪
- ♪ Oh, no ♪
- ♪ No, no ♪
♪ It's taking its toll
on me deep down ♪
- ♪ In my soul. ♪
-Brockman.
Brockman!
Today is your lucky day.
I got a FRAGO for you
and Corporal Selby here.
I've got no one else to cover
down for Godina today
on a malfunctioning GPR unit.
Swing by the armory. Gear up.
Great. Um...
Brockman.
Look...
Piece of advice,
you may outrank me,
but the least you can do is
button your blouse correctly.
Oh, shit.
Man, this... Hey, yo,
this BDC reticle is fire,
and this stock is heavier
than the standard issue,
so I have more control.
Lee...
I got a feeling
I ain't in Kansas anymore.
Okay. Calm down, Dorothy.
Dude, I got your back,
baby. Don't worry.
Yeah,
that's what I'm afraid of.
Wait. What happened
to Sergeant Godina?
He's sick.
What, Godina gets the shits
and we get you?
Dude's a lucky man.
Yeah, I'd rather have the shits
than be on a helicopter
right now.
Okay. Let's focus
on the mission, guys.
Okay.
Can we even call this a mission?
Do you take anything seriously?
No. But here's
what's gonna happen.
Okay, so G.I. Joker over here
and his sidekick...
I'm not a fucking sidekick.
Yeah, you are.
Anyways, you're gonna
run around acting all tough
because they think
that the Deltas
are gonna be watching them,
when in reality, they're not.
And you are gonna be
on the ground
for, like, 20 minutes.
Just do yourself a favor
and leave this shit behind.
That's not gonna happen.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Okay, what about you, smart-ass?
Me? Ooh,
I am going to be daydreaming
of a seven-figure salary
in Silicon Valley
while I'm babysitting
this defense contractor
who's just gonna push
a couple of buttons
and pretend
like he's a fucking hero.
It's a bit
more complicated than that.
What? Repairing a radar unit
that tracks underground
activity is no joke.
And, more importantly...
...this dude right here wouldn't
last a week in Silicon Valley.
Ha-ha. Okay.
Joshua Weaver,
Quantico Systems,
Senior Signals Analyst
reporting for duty.
- Oh, wow.
- Shit.
So I'm gonna...
No, don't look at me.
That's your people.
- Him? No. Not my people.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
All right. Whatever.
I don't care.
I'm just here to get this unit
back up and running,
help the world sleep
a little better.
I think the world was sleeping
just fine without you.
Mmm.
You guys should get a room.
Maybe we should, you know,
save some money.
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ Okay, say no more ♪
♪ She's a lotus
and I'm the conductor ♪
♪ Of a magnum opus ♪
♪ Simply braggadocios ♪
♪ Why don't we take advantage
of this moment ♪
♪ And whatever you own
we owned it ♪
All right, let's do it.
♪ 'Cause nobody really cares ♪
- ♪ 'Cause nobody really cares ♪
- ♪ Mama, I'm on the big screen ♪
♪ I took a big swing
out of life ♪
♪ I'm doing big things
in my life ♪
♪ I deserve six rings
like I'm Mike... ♪
Brockman, Weaver, you're up!
- All right, you ready?
- You ready?
Never better. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ Okay, say no more ♪
Didn't you see
I just fell down back there?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
Let's just get this
GPR unit back on line
and just head back home.
I mean, you're welcome
to help if you want.
Here. Take it.
No? That's right.
Yeah, it definitely seems
like a hardware issue.
Yeah, no, definitely
a hardware issue.
Like those frayed cables
in your hand. Great.
Hardware.
Okay. Strip them down,
and then I'll update
the software.
Come on, man.
It's pretty basic shit.
PILOT [over radio]:
Master Sergeant,
extreme weather is
coming in fast.
Condor is pulling the plug.
Let's go.
Copy that.
Brockman,
weather's coming in fast.
We gotta get out of here.
Roger that.
We're coming back now.
- All right. Pulling the plug.
- What?
- Why?
- Because we got orders.
Just connect those wires
and you're back in business.
Officially just became
somebody else's job, so...
Let's go.
So this is being all you can be.
Yep.
Great.
Go, go, go!
Let's go, let's go.
Let's hustle, Weaver.
Let's go.
All right. We're good.
We're good.
Wheels up, wheels up.
MAN [over radio]:
Turn right, heading 270.
Caution. High-risk wind shear
activity in your area.
Copy, Alpha One. Heading 270.
We're experiencing
severe turbulence.
Requesting vectors
for alternate flight paths.
- This is normal, right?
- Yep. We're okay.
Mayday! Mayday!
Mayday! Engine failure.
We've lost both engines!
No, no, no. Fuck.
Oh, shit. Selby, Selby,
Selby, wake up.
Selby?
- Selby.
- Hmm? What?
Stop. Stop.
Shit.
Look at me...
We gotta get out of here.
- Follow my lead.
- Yeah, yeah.
Selby...
I can't. No, I can't.
X-ray. X-ray, you on comms?
Fuck.
Lee.
Shh. Shh.
Weaver.
Hey. Weaver.
What the fuck just happened?
- Are you good? You good?
- Yeah.
Okay. Have you seen Ross?
Who the fuck is Ross?
Help!
Ross.
Ross. Ross!
Fuck!
Ross. Ross. Hey, hey.
I got you. I got you.
I've got you.
Oh, shit. Shit. My ribs.
Weaver.
Look at me. Look at me.
- You okay?
-  Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Look at me.
- You're good.
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
I need some help over here!
- Stay right here.
- Okay.
What do we got, Selby?
Help me move him
away from the helicopter.
-Ready?
- Three, two, one. Go!
Go, go, go, go. There we go.
Chief?
Chief.
Hold still. Hold still, Chief.
Okay.
Here we go. Ready, Chief?
Three, two, one.
Okay.
-Hey!
-Go, go, go, go!
Master Sergeant!
Come on. I got you.
- Okay. Okay. Here we go.
- No, no, no, no.
It's going through my hip.
Okay.
Chief?
Selby has him.
He's pretty banged up, sir.
Fuck. Go and get
the crash can
and bring me a satellite phone.
- Yes, sir.
- Quick.
Jesus.
It's okay, it's okay.
Here you go, sir.
Condor, talk.
This is Valiant One
on an unsecured line.
We are down. We are down.
Request immediate medevac.
MAN [over phone]: Valiant One,
medevac is unavailable
for your current coordinates.
You are outside
U.S. and ROK airspace.
I repeat, you are outside
New exfil location
is grid square 3763.
Delta Forces will be waiting.
Copy.
Valiant One out.
They're not coming.
No.
- This is Sergeant Brockman.
- They're not coming.
This is Sergeant Brockman.
Valiant One.
We have multiple injured.
We need medevac immediately.
MAN [over phone]: Repeat,
medevac is unavailable.
Proceed to grid square 3763.
- Delta Forces will be waiting.
- No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck that, Condor.
We have multiple dead!
Multiple wounded!
We need a medevac right now!
- Stop, stop, stop.
- Right now!
They can't get us.
We're in North Korea.
Hang that up. Hang that up.
Look at me.
Even if a rescue team
could make it past their SAMs,
coming to get us
would be an act of war.
If we didn't
already start one, okay?
So you're gonna have to
get these people out of here.
No, you're gonna
get us out of here.
You're gonna get us-- Selby!
Selby. Selby,
I need your help.
I need your help!
Brockman, just calm down, okay?
Calm down.
Chief?
-He's banged up.
- How bad?
Compound fractures in both legs
and probably head trauma.
But he's stable.
Ah, fuck. Okay.
Sir, I'll be right back, okay?
Just... Just one second.
Hey, even if I could
get in there,
his pulse is too weak and
he's hemorrhaging internally.
I'll keep him stable
till medevac gets here.
There's... there's not
gonna be a medevac.
- What?
Wait. Wait, what? Uh...
What-what the fuck
does that mean?
It means we're in North Korea.
That's what it means.
They can't just, like,
leave us here, right?
Give me that.
I'll call my team in Seoul.
- They'll definitely...
- You listen to me.
Orders were
to stay radio silent.
We're heading
to grid square 3763.
How far?
I... I have no idea.
And fucking what?
They'll come get us there?
I don't know.
What the fuck do you know?
Fuck.
Brockman.
Listen to me.
The North Koreans will
already be on their way.
And I need you
to do something for me.
My grandfather gave this
to my father.
He passed it on to me.
And I need you to get this
to my little boy.
Okay?
Don't let it end here.
And, uh,
I want you to tell him that
his daddy loves him very much.
More than anything in the world.
You can do this.
You just gotta trust
your instincts.
- I'm not trained for this.
- Yes, you are.
That rank on your chest
makes you the leader.
Okay?
Right now, you're the leader.
So you gotta be that for them.
And for yourself.
Sir, respectfully, I-I'm...
In charge now.
You're in charge.
I know there's a lot going on
in your brain right now.
Your emotions are high,
and all that shit.
You gotta put that away, okay?
You deal with that
when you get home,
because right now,
you stay in the trees
as much as you can.
You use it as cover.
You get out there,
you keep moving,
no matter what happens,
and you get your people
to that exfil.
Because my boys will be there.
They...
I promise you that.
I'm gonna buy you some time.
Hand me a frag.
No. We gotta get you
out of here.
Stop. Don't move me.
Please don't move me.
Look, it's okay.
Come on.
I can't use my left hand.
I need you to unwrap it.
You got this.
You just get to exfil,
and Delta will be there,
I promise you that.
Get yourself home, kid.
Yes, sir.
Come on.
What about Lebold?
- He's not coming.
- What...
- Shit.
-Maybe we, uh...
Maybe we just give up...
...and let the U.S.
negotiate us out.
Okay. Fuck this guy.
Come on.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hold up, hold up.
Brockman. Are we going
the right way?
Brockman.
Are we going the right way?
I was trained to analyze data
and update hardware.
Not this. All right?
So if you guys could just
give me a goddamn minute
to figure out where the fuck
we are, that would be great.
Hey, we're gonna be dead
in a goddamn minute.
Yeah. Those fucking
helicopters are everywhere.
We were told
to follow these coordinates
to the exfil, all right?
If we get there,
Delta will bring us home.
If we get there?
This guy is cooked.
Who's up next?
That's not how this works.
Get Chief up.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Okay. Okay. Hold on. Hold on.
Wait. Wait.
Let me get this straight.
Okay. Guys, guys.
Wait. Wait. Hold...
- We are going deeper into...
- Shut your mouth.
We are going deeper
into North Korea,
following a guy
who has very little education,
very little experience
and no idea
what the fuck he's doing.
This is fucking stupid.
Right? I mean...
Please, man, just get back
on that fucking sat phone,
- and tell them to pick us up!
- That sat phone is traceable.
You know that!
Those North Koreans
are praying to God
we fucking are stupid enough
to use it.
Seriously. Come on, man.
I'm right.
You know I'm right. Right?
It's what he says.
Let's fucking go.
-Our Father...
- Fuck.
...who art in heaven...
...hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done...
...on earth as it is in heaven.
Oh, fuck.
Give us this day
our daily bread...
...and forgive us
our trespasses...
...as we forgive those...
who trespass against us.
BROCKMAN [whispering]:
Weaver, get back.
The fuck, man?
- What the fuck?
- I don't know.
What the fuck?
Hey.
WEAVER [whispering]:
Over here. Over here.
Lead us not into temptation...
...but deliver us from evil.
BROCKMAN [softly]:
Stay down.
We're clear.
I'm gonna kill him.
You selfish bitch.
You stupid bastard...
I just, I told you I thought
that we should give ourselves up
and let the U.S. negotiate
our release. -Fuck that shit.
Listen to me.
Listen to me, man, okay?
Giving up... Giving up
makes way more fucking sense
than dying out there, man.
No, no, no. Not for me, man.
I'm Korean American.
I get caught here,
they'll literally fuck me
up the ass with a pole
and then wave me around
like a fucking flag.
No. No, dude.
We're protected
by the Geneva Convention.
No, we're not. North Korea
doesn't give a shit
about the Geneva Convention.
Capturing us
is exactly what they want.
And when they get ahold of you,
they're gonna squeeze
your fucking brain
for every last bit of intel
and send you back a vegetable.
So go ahead.
Be my fucking guest.
We're moving out. Let's go.
Good luck in that
torture chamber, asshole.
Oh, shit.
How are we supposed
to get Chief down there?
Okay.
No. Oh, God.
We gotta go.
We gotta get better cover.
Come on. Let's go. Come on.
Get back here.
- Lee. Get back.
- They can fucking see us.
Fuck.
Shh.
Hurry! Get him back!
Be careful with him.
Shh. Shh, shh.
You little fucker.
Don't fucking move.
I'm not fucking moving.
Don't do it. Don't do it.
Fuck.
- Okay?
- Shit. Fuck.
Are you good?
-Oh, fuck.
- Yeah.
We're fucking great.
Ready?
Let's go.
This is
fucking insane, you know.
I'm so used to just being
behind keyboards.
Listen.
"No matter how hard it gets,
"you stick your chest out,
you keep your head up,
and you handle it."
Okay?
Was that supposed to be
a pep talk?
It's Tupac.
How did that work out for him?
That's too far, man.
- I'm just saying, I mean...
-Guys.
I see something.
All right. What do you think?
It's your call.
It's a really
fucking open field.
Chief is in bad shape.
You have to make a decision.
And we will follow you
either way.
Okay. Okay. We hole up
in that barn for the night.
But we gotta go now before
these birds circle back.
- Okay.
- Good?
-Okay?
Stay low.
Go, go.
Go, go, go.
Go.
♪ See I'm looking
in the darkness ♪
♪ So cold, so heartless ♪
♪ I'm about to
run the gauntlet... ♪
This is crazy.
♪ Gotta make it
through the night ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm ready
for the fight ♪
♪ Watch out for the bites ♪
♪ They will end your life ♪
Secure the barn.
♪ Yeah! ♪
Set.
Go!
♪ Yeah! ♪
-Clear?
-Clear.
Thank God. Let's go get him.
Bring in Chief.
Come on.
Easy. Okay. Come down here.
Easy. Okay.
How you doing, Chief?
Okay. You just hang in there
and I'm gonna get you square.
Okay.
- He's seizing! He's seizing!
-Shit!
Help me! Put him on his side.
Put him on his side.
Okay. Hold him.
Okay. Okay.
Hold his arm... Okay.
Everybody relax.
I'll fucking drop him!
No, Ross.
Just chill out, okay?
What is he saying?
What the fuck?
How the fuck should I know?
He's Korean
and you're Korean, you know.
My grandparents are Korean, man.
I'm from fucking Gardena.
Fucking shit.
What does that mean?
I asked him for a beer.
Fucking shit.
It's the only thing I know, man.
Wave that thing at me again
and I'm putting him
the fuck down!
Ross, please, chill.
- Selby, what's going on?
- Need one more second.
Just hang in there, Chief.
Lee, tell him to put
his gun down in Korean.
Hey, motherfucker,
put the fucking gun down, man.
Shit.
Fuck. Fuck.
Okay.
I'm gonna fucking shoot him.
I'm gonna fucking shoot him!
One, two...
Ross,
fucking calm the fuck down!
You sure he's not gonna shoot?
He's not gonna shoot!
Stay in your fucking lane, bro!
One, two, three...
Ross, think! He would have
already pulled the trigger!
Okay! Okay!
Okay. Okay.
- What the fuck?
- Look. Right here.
It's okay.
Relax. Okay?
Brockman.
What the fuck are you doing?
We are not here to hurt you.
- All right?
-One, two, three...
Please. We need your help.
If you could just
put your gun down.
Fucking...
Chief.
Two, three...
Just please...
Please, just...
Just put it down.
Just put it down. It's okay.
It's okay.
There you go. There you go.
Yeah. I got it.
- There you go.
-Fuck me.
- It's okay.
-Come on. Come on.
Thank you.
Come on. We gotta
get you home. Come on.
- You just keep breathing.
-Selby.
Come on. I can do this.
I can do this.
Selby.
Selby, that's enough.
Stop. It's enough!
What? What?
He's gone.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no.
You did good. Yeah.
I... I know.
Fuck! He's running!
- Oh, fuck me!
- Shit!
No, no, no! You stay! Stay!
Selby! I got him!
Securing the house.
Lee, take him.
Clear.
- Ross?
-Clear.
-Help! Guys!
-Shit.
Go, go, go!
Back the fuck up!
All right, all right!
Get the fuck over here!
Shut the fuck up!
All right, all right, all
right, all right, all right.
Ross.
Lady, chill the fuck out.
-Shut the fuck up!
-Ross.
Let's gently, gently move them
into the living room, okay?
Hey.
We'll keep them there
until we leave in the morning.
Okay.
Come on. Come on.
- Come on.
What are they doing?
They won't move!
Come on. Come on!
Do you hear that?
What the fuck is that?
Shit.
It's coming from the floor.
Oh, God.
It's coming
from the fucking floor!
Lee, grab the bed. Lee!
What the fuck is that?
Show your face!
Show your head!
- Show your face!
- Shut the fuck up!
Show me your goddamn face!
Show me your fucking face
or I'll blow your brains out!
Show me your fucking face!
It's a kid.
Okay.
Hey, hey.
I'm so sorry.
There you go.
- Go to your mama.
- Omma!
Shit.
Okay. All right.
Fuck.
It's all right.
You good?
Mmm.
Okay.
Yo.
It's Miller time.
Come on, man. It's funny.
You get it. Asking that
Korean guy for a beer.
Wow. Did you rehearse
that one inside?
Well, I'm...
I'm funny. It's funny.
- I'm funny.
- No, you're not.
Um...
Om, nom, nom, nom.
Ah!
Wow!
My grandma used to
listen to this song.
Oh, um...
Come... Come sit.
Yeah, look... Face that way.
Yeah.
Okay. Uh... There you go.
Who knew that, um, protein
bars and a little music
would be the great unifier.
I think we all just want
the same thing.
Oh, really? What's that?
For you to shut up.
That's good.
That's really good.
I was gonna say "Love,"
- but I appreciate the dig.
-Uh-huh.
No, no, go ahead.
I deserve it.
How did you know
he wasn't gonna shoot?
I just saw a man
who had something to live for.
Kind of like we all do.
Yeah.
Hey, let me ask
you two something.
You both seem pretty smart.
Why choose this?
Following Daddy?
Dad was an alcoholic.
Did us all a favor
and died when I was little.
- Oh, hey, I'm sorry. I...
-No, no.
It's fine.
Where I come from, there just
isn't a lot of options.
You either...
get stuck at some
shitty restaurant or...
...you throw on a uniform.
So...
I chose this.
Damn.
That's pathetically cliché.
Yeah, that kind of
seems to be my brand, huh?
What about you, Selby?
What's your sob story?
I was born in Vietnam.
- I was adopted as a baby...
- No shit.
...and I was brought
to the States.
Our country
has given me so much,
and I wanted to give back.
- Hmm.
- That was deep.
And my story
was pathetically cliché?
- I'm just asking for a friend.
- Okay, okay.
Ooh-wah.
- Don't. No.
- No. Don't say that.
- What is wrong with you?
- I...
- It's cool, but...
- Doesn't feel cool.
Just you never say that again.
Okay.
All right.
We're out before sunrise.
So, uh, I'm gonna go
take over for Ross.
- You two get some shut-eye.
- Okay.
Cool.
How you doing out here?
Well, you know,
just freezing my dick off.
Yeah, can't really help you
with that.
All right, I'll take over
from here.
Get some rest, all right?
Roger that.
Hey.
Good work today.
Yeah. You, too.
Go get some rest.
Oh, shit.
They're coming.
We've got to go.
We've got to fucking go
right now!
Come on, Selby. Let's go.
No, I need my med kit.
Fuck!
No!
I have to go.
I have to go. No, no.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Are you kidding me?
They got Chief's body.
Fuck.
No.
Man, fuck these guys.
Fuck.
No, no, no, no.
Where's Selby?
Shh. I got you. I got you.
Selby. Selby. Hey. Hey.
I got you. Hey, look,
we're surrounded. All right?
-Okay.
-No, no, no, no.
Look at me. Come on.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
We're gonna have to fight our
way out of this. All right?
I got you. I got you.
She'll be safer in there, okay?
Okay.
Lee, back door.
Ross.
Hey. I need you to cover me.
I need you to cover me, okay?
- Okay.
- She's gonna be fine.
Let's go. Come on.
"
by Doechii playing]
-Ready? You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
♪ Then I ball like Spalding ♪
♪ Can't call my bluff,
this is my callin' ♪
♪ Won't duck, bitch,
I'm all in ♪
♪ It's a brand-new day,
new pace, light joggin' ♪
♪ Straight facts, no jargon ♪
♪ It's a whole lot of big
blue checks, no login ♪
♪ Low stress, no stallin' ♪
♪ See a whole lot of big
Bugattis when I walk in... ♪
♪ Crazy, got 'em goin' crazy ♪
♪ None these hatin'-ass bitches
gon' phase me ♪
♪ Huh! ♪
♪ Crazy, got 'em
going crazy, huh ♪
Clear.
Ross!
Oh, shit.
The truck.
He's going for the radio!
Cover, Selby!
Stop!
Brockman!
Let's, uh...
Let's get these bodies
into the barn.
Let's get the fuck home.
Hey, you good?
No.
How do I look?
Korean.
That's not helpful.
Okay.
Ready?
Good. Let's go.
Let's get that braid out.
Let's go.
Lee, what's going on?
Come on, let's go.
It's not working.
- It's not working, boss.
- Dude, come on,
- get this shit moving.
- All right.
Before they send more troops.
- What's she saying?
-What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait. No, no.
What?
Hmm?
It's a wood-burning truck.
This is just...
This is just fantastic.
- Fuck.
- Just a beacon in the sky now.
At least this piece of shit
fits in.
♪ Walk through the valley ♪
♪ Hope, hold on to me ♪
♪ The ashes surround us ♪
♪ But there is peace here... ♪
Fuck.
Hey, you, um...
You want me to take a look?
Yeah, if you don't mind.
Yeah. Yeah, just...
Damn.
Something caught that bullet
and saved your ass.
Well, there's, uh,
good news and bad news.
Bad news is sat phone's dead.
And the good news?
Uh, you're not.
-Brockman.
-What's going on?
Behind us.
Okay.
What's...
What's happening?
You're gonna need this.
All right, Lee. Pull over.
Oh, shit.
Fucker!
-Come on.
- Fucker. He's running!
- Fuck.
- Shit.
Let's go.
Hey, stay right here
and keep Binna safe.
-Come on, let's go.
-Let's go!
Where the fuck did he go?
- You see him?
- No.
I don't see shit, man.
Let's go. Come on, let's go.
Shit. Shit.
Fuck.
Breathe, Weaver.
Breathe, breathe.
- Okay, okay.
-  Selby.
Sel... Selby.
- Sel...
- Selby.
Yeah?
Hey, hey.
Shh.
Fuck.
All right, grid square's close.
We move out on foot.
Chest out, head up.
Okay.
- Ross.
-You're okay.
Okay.
We're almost there.
Hey.
Okay.
This is it.
I mean, this is, this is where
Condor told us to come.
- Dude, are you sure?
-Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I've read
this map a thousand times.
Where are they? You said
they were gonna come get us.
Lebold said
that they were gonna come.
You said they were gonna come...
Lebold said
they were coming, Ross!
Just look for something
out of the ordinary.
Out of the ordinary?
We have a fucking kid now.
Look at Selby's fucking face.
What the fuck is wrong
with my fucking face?
We're in fucking North Korea,
okay? That's my point.
-Brockman.
- What?
You gotta give us
more than that, man.
I'm trying.
Oh, my God.
I don't think they were
ever gonna come here.
I think we were supposed
to meet them.
Can someone fucking translate
what he's saying?
Lee, if this GPR unit is right,
there's something running
underneath us that is man-made
that is going north
to south right now.
Like a fifth incursion tunnel.
Oh, fuck.
We need to look for something
that is either metal
or concrete.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
On the surface.
Let's start looking.
There's nothing
out here, Brockman.
This is a waste of time.
What are you doing,
man? Come on.
Let's go. Get your
shit together. Get up.
Bro, get your ass up.
Give me a minute.
All right. Jesus.
Binna?
Oh, fuck! Binna! Binna!
Get this off! Come on.
Come on.
Binna!
Oh, my God. Okay.
Let's get down there. Let's go.
Holy shit.
We found it.
Incursion tunnel number five.
Guys, this is our way home.
This goes right under
the DMZ to South Korea.
This thing's going haywire.
Shit.
Does anybody know
which way south is?
No?
All right.
Going forward. Selby, on me.
You guys got the back?
What do you think that stuff is?
I don't know, ammo crates?
They're ready for a war.
Wait, wait, wait.
You see what I see?
Yeah.
Holy shit.
We did it.
Oh, my God, we're going home.
Oh, fuck, we're going home.
Delta.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Contact front!
Shit!
Go, go, go, go!
Last man! Last man!
Take this. Lee! Grab her!
Okay.
Last man!
Let's go, let's go!
Come on.
Shit!
- I'm out!
- Brockman, I'm dry!
- I'm out, too!
- Fuck.
Brockman! Get up! Let's go!
Just go!
Go! Get out of here!
I'm gonna buy you some time!
It's a fucking order!
Fuck! Binna, go!
Go, go!
Ugh! Piece of shit!
Let's go! Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Brockman! Brockman!
We got you. Let's go.
One male. Caucasian.
Bullet wound on the
right side, he's bleeding.
Stabilize him quickly.
SOLDIER [on radio]: Bravo
team, this is Alpha team.
We have wounded. Over.
Keep moving! Keep moving!
Move it!
We got him.
Bringing him out now.
We got one coming through.
Let's go home.
♪ I'm checking my vital signs,
drawing my battle lines ♪
♪ Going to war again ♪
♪ Feeling the rhythm
inside of my chest ♪
♪ All I need is just a pen ♪
♪ I know I was born for this ♪
♪ I know
I was born for this ♪
♪ Don't care for the critics,
my words are like physics ♪
♪ A force that they can't stop ♪
♪ They just don't get it,
I think they forget ♪
♪ I'm not done till I'm on top ♪
♪ I know I was born for this ♪
♪ I know
I was born for this ♪
♪ I believe, I believe
we can write our story ♪
we can be an army ♪
♪ We are the warriors
who learned to love the pain ♪
♪ We come from different places
but have the same name ♪
♪ 'Cause we were,
'cause we were, 'cause we were ♪
♪ 'Cause we were born for this ♪
♪ We were born for this ♪
♪ I've struggled for years
and through all of the tears ♪
♪ I've faced the doubts I hide ♪
♪ I never gave into
my fears deep within ♪
♪ 'Cause I heard
my voice inside ♪
♪ I know I was born for this ♪
♪ I know
I was born for this ♪
♪ I believe, I believe
we can write our story ♪
we can be an army ♪
♪ We are the warriors
who learned to love the pain ♪
♪ We come
from different places ♪
♪ But have the same name ♪
♪ 'Cause we were,
'cause we were, 'cause we were ♪
♪ 'Cause we were born for this ♪
♪ We were born for this ♪
♪ We are the broken ones
who chose to spark a flame ♪
♪ Watch as our fire rages,
our hearts are never tame ♪
♪ 'Cause we were,
'cause we were, 'cause we were ♪
♪ 'Cause we were born for this ♪
♪ We were born for this ♪
♪ We were born for this. ♪